{
    "subject": "resource/Jack_Dempsey_(politician)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/homepage",
    "object": "http://jackdempseymp.com/",
    "human_readable": "The homepage of Jack Dempsey (politician) is http://jackdempseymp.com/.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9789584875106812,
            "question": "What is the homepage URL for Jack Dempsey (politician)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9631670713424683,
            "question": "Is there a website dedicated to Jack Dempsey (politician)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9574683308601379,
            "question": "Is http://jackdempseymp.com/ a valid URL for political information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9408602118492126,
            "question": "Does Jack Dempsey (politician) have an official website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9241501688957214,
            "question": "What is the domain name of Jack Dempsey's (politician) website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9204440712928772,
            "question": "Where can you find information about Jack Dempsey (politician) online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9069851040840149,
            "question": "What kind of content is likely found on http://jackdempseymp.com/?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8998364210128784,
            "question": "What is the web address for Jack Dempsey's political platform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8929880857467651,
            "question": "Can you access information about Jack Dempsey (politician)'s political activities online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.739763081073761,
            "question": "Where can you learn more about Jack Dempsey's (politician) stance on various issues?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The homepage of Jack Dempsey (politician) is http://jackdempseymp.com/.",
            "html": "dbpedia_741_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you access information about Jack Dempsey (politician)'s political activities online?",
            "html": "dbpedia_741_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the web address for Jack Dempsey's political platform?",
            "html": "dbpedia_741_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of content is likely found on http://jackdempseymp.com/?",
            "html": "dbpedia_741_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_741_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_741_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_741_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_741_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_741_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_741_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_741_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_741_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_741_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_741_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\nThe triple statement to be evaluated is:\n\"The homepage of Jack Dempsey (politician) is http://jackdempseymp.com/. \n\nBased on the provided context information, there are multiple mentions of \"Jack Dempsey\" but only one is related to a politician. This politician is referred to as \"Cr Dempsey\" and has a LinkedIn column called 'Jack hammer \u2013 drilling down on community issues'.\n\nHowever, none of the documents mention a homepage for Cr Dempsey, let alone http://jackdempseymp.com/. One document mentions that Cr Dempsey was denied running for Hinkler.\n\nTherefore, the correct response is:\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: There is no information provided about Jack Dempsey being a politician or that his homepage is at http://jackdempseymp.com/. The documents only provide information about Jack Dempsey as a boxer, including his birth and death details, boxing achievements, and his brother's work."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}